<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on p314d0</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on p314d0</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>IAM CreateAccessKey PrivEsc - Cybr</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/iam-createaccesskey-privesc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/iam-createaccesskey-privesc/</guid>
      
      <description>Exploit iam:CreateAccessKey to gain access to an Amazon S3 bucket containing sensitive data that your IAM user does not have permission to access. The flag is the credit card number of &amp;ldquo;Kayla Sánchez&amp;rdquo; found in the exfiltrated clients file.
Scenario Only high-level administrators should have the iam:CreateAccessKey permission, as an attacker with this permission for other users can create an Access Key ID and Secret Key for that user, allowing them to authenticate as that user.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IAM CreateLoginProfile PrivEsc - Cybr</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/iam-createloginprofile-privesc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/iam-createloginprofile-privesc/</guid>
      
      <description></description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/pages/about/</guid>
      
      <description>As a Penetration Tester, my experience extends to Web Application Security, where I leverage my frontend development background to create secure and user-friendly interfaces. I hold certifications such as eJPT, eWPT, and eWPTX, and I am also diving into the world of cloud security with certifications like ARTA and MCRTA. My goal is to explore and exploit security measures, ensuring users can navigate safely in today’s ever-evolving digital landscape. I created this blog to share my experiences and deepen my understanding of offensive security.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
